https://silkworth.net/privacy-policy/

AA Literature
A.A. Big Book
A.A. Big Book (164 Pages)
9th Step Promises
(Pg 83/84)
Timelines In A.A. History
Manuscript Of A.A. World History – Bob P.
Influential Books
A.A. Big Book (164 Pages)
John Barleycorn
The Confessions Of Saint Augustine (13 Books)
Religion, Clergy & A.A.
Free Stuff
Free Audiobooks & Speaker Tapes
Videos Of Bill Wilson
The PDF Project (1000+ PDF’s)
A.A. Big Book
A.A. Big Book (164 Pages)
9th Step Promises
(Pg 83/84)
Timelines In A.A. History
Manuscript Of A.A. World History – Bob P.
Influential Books
A.A. Big Book (164 Pages)
John Barleycorn
The Confessions Of Saint Augustine (13 Books)
Religion, Clergy & A.A.
Free Stuff
Free Audiobooks & Speaker Tapes
Videos Of Bill Wilson
The PDF Project (1000+ PDF’s)
Privacy Policy
This privacy statement has been created in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Silkworth.net (https://silkworth.net/).
The terms “we”, “us” and “our” refer to Silkworth.net.
The Information We Collect
This notice applies to all information collected on the Silkworth.net Web site or submitted to Silkworth.net at any time through any Service Pages.
At Silkworth.net’s Web site, we do not require personally identifiable information from you in order to access and use the Web site.
Personally Identifiable Information-When visiting Silkworth.net’s Web site and signing up for or using Silkworth.net services through any Service Page, you may choose to supply Silkworth.net with information that identifies you personally. This information may include your name and contact information, gender, birth date, user comments, and other information. Silkworth.net does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted unless you sign up for a Service offered from Silkworth.net. Information you supply at such time is at your own discretion. Many services offered from Silkworth.net, are from outside sources [external]. Please be sure to read their Terms of Service, agreements when signing up for their services.
Aggregate Information—We collect non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our Web site and services. We do not share this information with outside parties without your permission except to the extent that is necessary to administer the services we offer our Clients or to comply in responding to subpoenas, court orders or other legal proceedings.
From time to time, we also use the information you provide about yourself to inform you of additions or improvements to the Silkworth.net services as well as conduct member surveys in order to improve our services.
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways or for reasons unrelated to the ones described above without also providing an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
Collection of Personal Information from Children under Thirteen
Silkworth.net does not allow children known to be under the age of thirteen (13) to register for our services. We may momentarily capture personally identifiable information for purposes of determining whether a user is over the age of thirteen (13) and thus qualifies to use our services. Where the user is under the age of thirteen (13), such information is automatically deleted.
Security
Although this site collects no information about the visitor other than that discribed above, security measures have been put into place to protect the loss, misuse, excess to, and alteration of the information under our control. Some of the most sophisticated available security software has been installed. Although you do not need to supply this web site any personal information, it is unlikely that any information will be misappropriated.
How You Can Access or Update Your Information
If you have submitted information on our site but do not currently have an account with us, or you have lost your ID and\or password, you can access and correct the information that we collect and maintain by contacting us and requesting such information or correction.
To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections to your information.
How to Contact Us
Should you have other questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please contact us online.
Email, and Search Specific Terms and Conditions
Silkworth.net considers email transmitted via our service to be private correspondence between the sender and recipient. Therefore, we will not monitor, edit or disclose the contents of your private communications.
Content posted to public community areas is publicly available, and Silkworth.net reserves the right to remove any publicly posted content that it deems to be objectionable.
Advertisers
We use outside ad company’s to display ads and links to their web sites on our site. These ads and links may contain cookies. These third-party advertising companies employ cookie and 1×1 pixel . gifs or web beacons to measure and improve the effectiveness of ads for their clients. To do so, these companies may use anonymous information about your visits to our website and other websites. This information can include: date/time of banner ad shown, the banner ad that was shown, their cookie, the IP address. This information can also be used for online preference marketing purposes.
Cookies received with third party banner ads and/or links to web sites outside this web site are collected by those company’s and businesses and we do not have access to this information.
Although we collect no data of your visit, other than that already discribed in this Privacy Statement, external web sites that you visit may share some customer data with the advertising companies.
If you want to prevent a third-party advertiser from collecting data, currently you may either visit each ad network’s web site individually and opt out or visit the NAI gateway opt-out site to opt-out of all network advertising cookies. Click here for the NAI gateway opt-out site. This site will also allow you to review the third-party advertising companies’ privacy policies.
External Links
Silkworth.net contains links to other web sites and is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. Silkworth.net is not responsible for the information practices or the contents of any external site, merchant clients or their affiliates. All external sites may collect information from or about Internet users, including personal information. The collection, use, and disclosure of information by the owners/creators of all external sites are subject to their respective privacy policies.
When visiting such sites, it is urged that you be an informed surfer and use caution when providing any personal data.
Public Forums
Silkworth.net has and makes available chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.
